[OVERDO]
[Episode 23]
Those who wish to sever ties with the family
Must suffer 3 stab wounds.
The first stab today,
I give to myself.
I cannot choose my birth,
But I can at least
Choose how I live this life.
Qingyu.
In the past, I was despised by everyone.
Only you wanted me.
When I was framed,
Only you believed me.
When the tendons
In my hands were severed,
Only you
Tried to cure my hands till your death.
Qingyu.
I said
I would protect you.
I broke my promise.
Let this stab
Be my apology.
They all say that
A family should be
Like a warm harbor.
But since returning home at 12,
I've lived in hell every day.
Without you,
Why linger in hell?
This stab
Shall be the end
Of everything between us.
Come on.
[Funeral]
Are you afraid?
Come on!
Who says I'm afraid?
Cheng Jinzhi.
From today on,
Ashes to ashes,
Dust to dust.
We'll go our separate ways
And have nothing more to do with each other.
I will also have nothing to do
With the Murong family.
Inspector,
I found something unusual.
Speak.
As you ordered,
I carefully searched the wedding hall.
On the chair where the Marshal sat,
I found this.
A sniper rifle bullet?
That's right.
Huo Minxian's pistol doesn't use this kind of bullet.
This means there was another shooter at the scene,
Targeting the Marshal.
But...
But no gunshot was heard.
This means the sniper rifle was equipped with a silencer.
A gunsmith who can install a silencer
Without affecting
The gun's accuracy
Is very rare in all of Nancheng.
I'll investigate from the angle of firearm modifications.
Oh, right.
Regarding Qingyi...
And Ren Susu's whereabouts,
Let me know as soon as you find anything.
Understood.
Qingyi?
During the wedding,
What exactly were you doing?
It has nothing to do with you.
Ren Susu,
If you hadn't insisted on marrying Qingyu...
If you hadn't
Lured Huo Minxian here...
If you had died 3 years ago,
Qingyu wouldn't have died!
I wish the one who died
Was you, not him.
If thinking
And saying that
Can distract you from your pain for a second
And give you some comfort,
Then go ahead.
Ren Susu,
I'll ask you one last time.
Did you ever love me?
Three years ago,
I meant it.
What about now?
I thought God treated me well
By letting me meet you.
I thought I could be like a normal person
And have the right to love and be loved.
Qingyi,
Let yourself go.
Ren Susu, you know what?
From the very beginning,
I could never let go
Of the tiny sliver of hope
That I could live like a normal person.
But now,
I think I can let it go.
♪ The more passionate ♪
Ren Susu,
♪ Our past embrace ♪
I hate you.
♪ The more icy ♪
♪ Our present clash ♪
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
♪ Bind you and me ♪
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
♪ Together, we fall ♪
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
♪ Let the tears fall, let the blood spill ♪
♪ Even through suffering, I'll never let go of your hand ♪
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called a lifetime together ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Murong Qingyi, stop right there!
Go!
Beat him up!
Who gave you the nerve to make Mother so angry?
Beat him! Beat him to death!
♪ Hate is the smoke left by dying flames ♪
Stop!
Qingyi!
♪ Love is the warmth lingering after the wildfire ♪
♪ Love and hate collide in a blaze ♪
♪ Devour me all ♪
♪ Ahead lies a tangle of joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Behind remains the bitterness of unspoken feelings ♪
♪ The heart races with every thought ♪
♪ As long as we loved each other, I don't care ♪
♪ If it's a blessing or a curse ♪
Susu,
You should live a good life.
What counts as a good life?
Being healthy and safe,
Following your heart's desires,
Immersing yourself in what you love...
And if fate grants you the fortune
To meet your destined one,
Being together day and night.
This way,
♪ I happened to ♪
Even ordinary things
♪ Hear your name ♪
And simple meals
♪ And all the memories ♪
♪ Came flooding back ♪
Can be filled with
Endless affection.
♪ There I stood in the falling snow ♪
♪ Wrapped in my coat ♪
By this point,
♪ My heart pounding ♪
The scars,
Sorrows,
♪ Walking down that old road ♪
Hatred,
♪ Stopping every few steps ♪
And fears of the past
Will all fade away
Like passing clouds.
♪ In the misty train car ♪
♪ I wish I could ask you once more ♪
♪ If you have any ♪
Qingyi...
Don't be afraid.
♪ New corny jokes to tell ♪
You're awake.
You saved me?
Where is Qingyi?
He's fine.
I sent him to the hospital.
You'd better worry about yourself first.
You're badly injured.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
Death would have been
Too easy on you.
What do you mean?
Have you seen this before, Miss Fang?
I found it in the wedding hall.
Back then, you wanted to shoot
And assassinate my father.
But Huo Minxian suddenly appeared.
My father turned around to check on her
And narrowly escaped the assassination.
I only realized today that
On the day of the wedding,
I almost lost 2 of my closest relatives.
Miss Ren.
Please explain
Your vicious behavior.
I just wanted to kill Li Rongzhang.
I wanted to before,
And I want to even more now.
Li Rongzhang...
Deserves to die.
Ren Susu.
My father has no grudge against you.
No grudge?
Twelve years ago,
The North-South Railway bombing case
Claimed nearly a hundred innocent lives.
If we talk about grudges,
Li Rongzhang doesn't have enough to answer for.
Nonsense!
The North-South Railway bombing case
Was settled long ago.
You have no proof;
How can you blame my father?
Inspector Li.
When Qingyu was alive,
He said you were upright,
But lacked decisiveness.
He was right.
You only believe what you want to believe.
How dare you mention him to me?
Answer me.
Is Huo Minxian
Related to you?
Was Qingyu
Killed by you?
Qingyu's death
Was not in my plan.
I also don't know why Huo Minxian
Suddenly appeared.
If you really want to avenge Qingyu,
You should investigate Huo Minxian
Instead of wasting your time arguing with me.
You're still muddying the waters.
Do you really think I wouldn't shoot you?
In our original plan,
I was supposed to die.
[Ji'an Hospital]
[Murong Qingyu was martyred]
[Aviation school left without an owner, future uncertain]
Young Master Qingyi,
You're awake.
How did I get back here?
You had already fainted when I found you.
You were badly injured.
Was I alone?
Yes.
I knew it.
We will never
See each other again in this life.
So be it.
Move.
Let me in.
Move!
Who's outside?
It's Ms. Ye.
I had someone stop her.
Murong Qingyi!
[Murong Qingyu was martyred]
[Aviation school left without an owner, future uncertain]
Murong Qingyi.
We need you.
I'm already a useless person.
How can I help you?
Now, various forces want to take over the aviation school.
Li Rongzhang even gathered a bunch of people
To surround the aviation school.
But the aviation school is not privately owned.
In the past, it was just a hot potato
That everyone despised.
Qingyu took over the aviation school
And put in so much work
To turn the school
Into what it is today.
If we let Li Rongzhang and the others do what they want,
The aviation school will fall apart.
So what?
Isn't it good if it falls apart?
You...
Your brother
Devoted his heart and soul to the aviation school.
Are we really going to let others take advantage of the situation?
What's the point
Of saying this now?
Of course there is!
The current few batches of students at the aviation school
Are exceptionally well-trained.
Disregarding combat experience,
Their quality is comparable to that of a regular air force.
If they are disbanded
Or used
By people with ulterior motives,
-Qingyu's spirit won't be at ease. -Enough.
When Qingyu was alive,
He never thought about himself for a single day.
You people
Always pressured him with family responsibilities and national duties.
Now that he's dead,
Can't he rest?
Okay.
I see what you mean.
Qingyu is gone.
If his legacy
Disappears as well,
He'd truly be forgotten.
[Special Care Unit]
Wait.
I'll go.
[Tongde Hospital]
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were pregnant.
Why didn't you tell me earlier
That you were pregnant with Qingyu's child?
What did you say?
Don't worry.
The doctor did everything they could
And saved the baby.
Sister-in-law,
As long as I'm here,
I won't let anyone bully you.
I will definitely protect you and the baby.
You should go.
I want to be alone for a while.
Inspector Li.
The mother and the fetus are both fine.
They just need a good rest.
However,
This lady
Has severe damage to her right cochlea.
I'm afraid
She will suffer permanent hearing loss.
Is there really no other way?
The chances of a full recovery are very low.
Director Zhang.
Regarding what you saw
And heard today,
Please keep them a secret.
I understand.
Qingyu.
Don't worry.
Since I promised you to take care of this family,
I will definitely keep your unborn child
Safe.
[Two months later]
News Agency Briefs.
Murong Qingyi will carry out his brother's last wishes.
He plans to lead several student soldiers from the aviation school
To the southwestern front in 3 days
To answer the nation's special wartime call-up
And support the war effort.
Sister-in-law.
The doctor said
A quiet environment is better for your recovery.
I know
You're angry.
Qingyu died suddenly.
Like you,
I am also very sad.
That's why I did the stupid thing
Of interrogating you for answers.
So, you must take good care of your health.
I will definitely be responsible
For you and the child's future.
What if this child isn't Qingyu's?
What do you mean?
I mean,
If this child isn't Qingyu's,
Will you still be responsible to the end?
You betrayed Qingyu?
There had never been any affection
Between Qingyu and me.
This child
Is Murong Qingyi's.
Triumph for our heroes,
Safe return for all!
[Answer the summons to fight for our country]
Triumph for our heroes,
Safe return for all!
[Answer the summons to fight for our country]
♪ The more passionate ♪
♪ Our past embrace ♪
♪ The more icy ♪
Ren Susu.
♪ Our present clash ♪
I hate you.
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
Stop the car.
♪ There is no escaping it ♪